{
    "subject": "resource/The_Wizard_of_Gore_(2007_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Wizard of Gore (2007 film) is a Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8352710008621216,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8194941878318787,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8178822994232178,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7508251667022705,
            "question": "What year was the film 'The Wizard of Gore' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44862091541290283,
            "question": "Are there any actors known for their roles in 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3967359662055969,
            "question": "Is 'The Wizard of Gore' a real event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37840592861175537,
            "question": "How is 'The Wizard of Gore' received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.327414870262146,
            "question": "Where can one watch 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30391955375671387,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22256574034690857,
            "question": "Has 'The Wizard of Gore' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Wizard of Gore (2007 film) is a Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6114_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in 'The Wizard of Gore'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6114_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can one watch 'The Wizard of Gore'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6114_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is 'The Wizard of Gore' received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6114_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6114_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!  I'm here to help."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query asks whether the information in the documents supports the triple that \"The Wizard of Gore (2007 film)\" is a \"Film\".\n\nGiven the context, the answer is yes.\n\nHere's the response in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe text mentions \"The Wizard of Gore,\" which is identified as a remake and refers to it as a film, supporting the statement that \"The Wizard of Gore (2007 film) is a Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}